Aaron Ziegelman Foundation collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Manuscripts
  - Finding Aid (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Subseries 5: Luboml Memorial Book
      - "Luboml: The Memorial Book of a Vanished Shtetl". Published Version, 1997, 227 leaves (Box-folder 28/417)
      - Cover Art, 1997, 1 leaf (1 negative, 2 black and white prints) (Box-folder 28/418)
    - Subseries 6: Donor Files
      - Loan Agreements, 1997, 117 leaves (Box-folder 29/419)
      - Becker, Ruby L, January, 1996-1997, 8 leaves (Box-folder 29/420)
      - Borman, Ruth, October 1995, 3 leaves (Box-folder 29/421)
      - Buchstein, S H, Undated, 4 leaves (Box-folder 29/422)
      - Cymerboin, Lew, 1935, 1992, 1995, 1996, 13 leaves (Box-folder 29/423)
      - Freedman, Frank, 1935-1996, 30 leaves (Box-folder 29/424)
      - Friedman, Thelma, 1994-1997, 5 leaves (Box-folder 29/425)
      - Ginsberg, Leon, 1994-1996, 12 leaves (Box-folder 29/426)
      - Dzei, Mikola (Folder 1 of 5), Various dates, 1993-1995, 62 leaves (19 color prints, 1 black and white print) (Box-folder 29/427)
      - Dzei, Mikola Various dates (Folder 2 of 5), 69 leaves (Box-folder 29/428)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish, Ukrainian, Russian and Yiddish.
      - Dzei, Mikola, Various dates (Folder 3 of 5), 44 leaves (Box-folder 29/429)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Ukrainian, Russian, Polish and Hebrew.
      - Dzei, Mikola, Various dates (Folder 4 of 5), 80 leaves (5 color prints) (Box-folder 29/430)
      - Dzei, Mikola, Various dates (Folder 5 of 5), 119 leaves (Box-folder 29/431)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Ukrainian, Polish, Russian and Hebrew.
      - Getman, Abraham, Various dates (Folder 1 of 3), 163 leaves (Box-folder 30/432)
      - Getman, Abraham (Folder 2 of 3), 3 leaves (30 color prints) (Box-folder 30/433)
        The manuscript materials are in Ukrainian and Yiddish with English translation.
      - Getman, Abraham: Various dates (Folder 3 of 3), Undated, 161 leaves (Box-folder 30/434)
      - Getman, Abraham - "Borders of Hope" Draft, 139 leaves (Box-folder 30/435)
      - Getman, Abraham - "Borders of Hope" - Published Copy, Undated, 135 leaves (Box-folder 30/436)
      - Gitalis, Chana, 2000, 10 leaves (Box-folder 30/437)
        The manuscript materials are in Yiddish with Hebrew and English translations.
      - Glass, Sydney, 1995-1996, 2 leaves (Box-folder 30/438)
      - Goodman, May Schuster, 1996, 31 leaves (8 color prints) (Box-folder 30/439)
      - Grisham, Kay, 1997, 1 leaf (Box-folder 30/440)
      - Hetman, Aviva, Undated, 37 leaves (19 color prints) (Box-folder 30/441)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish, Hebrew, and Yiddish.
      - Karpus, Yossef, Various dates, 1996, 66 leaves (Box-folder 30/442)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish, Hebrew and German.
      - Menachemi, Miki, 5 leaves (Box-folder 31/443)
      - Orbuch, Sonia, December 17, 1996, 1 leaf (Box-folder 31/444)
      - Ostapyuk, Alexander - Luboml district Museum, Various dates (Folder 1 of 2), 2001, 102 leaves (Box-folder 31/445)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Russian, Polish and Ukrainian.
      - Ostapyuk, Alexander - Luboml District Museum, Various dates (Folder 2 of 2), Various dates (Box-folder 31/446)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Russian, Ukrainian, Polish, Hebrew and Latin.
      - Perelman, Brenda Kandel, 1995-1996, 5 leaves (Box-folder 31/447)
      - Prager, Anita, 1995-1996, 9 leaves (1 color print) (Box-folder 31/448)
      - Reder, Edith Axelrod, 1997, 2 leaves (4 color prints; 9 color negative strips) (Box-folder 31/449)
      - Reimer, Annette, Undated, 33 leaves (10 color prints) (Box-folder 31/450)
      - Rodman, Rhea, 1997, 5 leaves (2 color prints) (Box-folder 31/451)
      - Rosenzweig, Benjamin, 1996-1997, 31 leaves (Box-folder 31/452)
      - Schechter, Frances, 1996, 4 leaves (Box-folder 31/453)
      - Sherman, Ruth Kagan, Undated, 8 leaves (Box-folder 31/454)
      - Stoller, Hy, 1995, 15 leaves (3 black and white prints). (Box-folder 31/455)
      - Tessler, Shoshana (Rose), 1999, 19 leaves (Box-folder 31/456)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish, Yiddish and Hebrew.
      - Trokh, Nikolai, 1994-1996, 2 leaves (8 color prints) (Box-folder 31/457)
      - Wolyn, Heichal, Undated, 8 leaves (29 color prints, 14 negative strips) (Box-folder 31/458)
        The manuscript materials are in Hebrew.
      - Various Photo Donors: Various dates, Undated, 73 leaves (Box-folder 31/459)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish, Hebrew, Yiddish and French.
    - Subseries 7: Transcripts
      - Lillian Ziegelman Chanales. 7/25/95. LLC – 1. (MV060, MV155) Transcript of Tape 1 of 3, 32 leaves (Box-folder 32/460)
      - Lillian Ziegelman Chanales. 7/25/95. LLC – 2. (MV061, MV155) Transcript of Tape 2 of 3, 34 leaves (Box-folder 32/461)
      - Lillian Ziegelman Chanales. 7/25/95. LLC – 3. (MV062, MV155) Transcript of Tape 3 of 3, 26 leaves (Box-folder 32/462)
      - Nathan Eiger. 7/17/95. LNE – 1. (MV030, MV156), 22 leaves (Box-folder 32/463)
      - Nathan Eiger. 7/17/95. LNE – 2. (MV031, MV156) Transcript of Tape 2 of 6, 30 leaves (Box-folder 32/464)
      - Nathan Eiger. 7/17/95. LNE – 3. (MV032, MV156) Transcript of Tape 3 of 6, Transcript of Tape 1 of 6, 25 leaves (Box-folder 32/465)
      - Nathan Eiger. 7/17/95. LNE – 4. (MV033, MV156) Transcript of Tape 4 of 6, 27 leaves (Box-folder 32/466)
      - Nathan Eiger. 7/17/95. LNE – 5. (MV034, MV157) Transcript of Tape 5 of 6, 19 leaves (Box-folder 32/467)
      - Nathan Eiger. 7/17/95. LNE – 6. (MV035, MV157) Transcript of Tape 6 of 6, 23 leaves (Box-folder 32/468)
      - Ann Friedman Gershengorn, 6/19/95, LAG – 1. (MV027, MV158, MV159) Table of Contents. Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 1 of 3, 31 leaves (Box-folder 32/469)
      - Copy 2 of Transcript of Tape 1 of 3, 31 leaves
      - Ann Friedman Gershengorn 6/19/95 LAG – 2 (MV028 and MV158 or MV159) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 2 of 3, 33 leaves (Box-folder 32/470)
      - Copy 2 of transcript of Tape 2 of 3, 33 leaves (Annotated)
      - Ann Friedman Gershengorn, 6/19/95, LAG – 3. (MV029, MV158, MV159) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 3 of 3, 29 leaves (Box-folder 32/471)
      - Copy 2 of transcript of Tape 3, 29 leaves (Annotated)
      - Victor Gershengorn, 6/19/95, LEP – 1. (MV071, MV160, MV168) Table of Contents, 6 leaves (Box-folder 32/472)
      - Victor Gershengorn, 6/19/95, LEP – 2. (MV072, MV160, MV168): Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 2 of 5, 32 leaves (Box-folder 32/473)
      - Victor Gershengorn, 6/19/95, LEP – 3. (MV073, MV160, MV168V) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 3 of 5, 34 leaves (Box-folder 32/474)
      - Victor Gershengorn, 6/19/95, LEP – 4. (MV074, MV160, MV168) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 4 of 5, 28 leaves (Box-folder 32/475)
      - Victor Gershengorn, 6/19/95, LEP – 5. (MV075, MV160, MV168) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 5 of 5, 11 leaves (Box-folder 32/476)
      - Abe Getman, 7/18/95, LAGE – 1. (MV094, MV169) Transcript of Tape 1 of 8, 28 leaves (Box-folder 32/477)
      - Abe Getman, 7/18/95, LAGE – 2. (MV095, MV169) Transcript of Tape 2 of 8, 28 leaves (Box-folder 32/478)
      - Abe Getman, 7/18/95, LAGE – 3. (MV096, MV169) Transcript of Tape 3 of 8, 34 leaves (Box-folder 32/479)
      - Abe Getman, 7/18/95, LAGE – 4. (MV097, MV169) Transcript of Tape 4 of 8, 30 leaves (Box-folder 32/480)
      - Abe Getman, 7/18/95, LAGE – 5. (MV098, MV170) Transcript of Tape 5 of 8, 22 leaves (Box-folder 32/481)
      - Abe Getman, 7/18/95, LAGE – 6. (MV099, MV170) Transcript of Tape 6 of 8, 21 leaves (Box-folder 32/482)
      - Abe Getman, 7/18/95, LAGE – 7. (MV100, MV170) Copy 1 of Transcript of Tape 7 of 8, 25 leaves (Box-folder 32/483)
      - Abe Getman, 7/18/95, LAGE – 8. (MV101, MV170) Transcript of Tape 8 of 8, 18 leaves (Box-folder 32/484)
      - May Shuster Goodman, 8/13/95, LMS – 1. (MV082, MV175) Transcript of Tape 1 of 5, 33 leaves (Box-folder 33/485)
      - May Shuster Goodman, 8/13/95, LMS – 2. (MV083, MV175) Transcript of Tape 2 of 5, 38 leaves (Box-folder 33/486)
      - May Shuster Goodman, 8/13/95, LMS – 3. (MV084, MV175) Transcript of Tape 3 of 5, 32 leaves (Box-folder 33/487)
      - May Shuster Goodman, 8/13/95, LMS – 4. (MV085, MV175) Transcript of Tape 4 of 5, 28 leaves (Box-folder 33/488)
      - May Shuster Goodman, 8/13/95, LMS – 5. (MV086, MV175V) Transcript of Tape 5 of 5, 17 leaves (Box-folder 33/489)
      - Esther Gribelkis Pachter, 8/15/95, LEPA – 1. (MV108, MV191) transcript of Tape 1 of 6, 31 leaves (Box-folder 33/490)
      - Esther Gribelkis Pachter, 8/15/95, LEPA – 2. (MV109, MV191) Transcript of Tape 2 of 6, 27 leaves (Box-folder 33/491)
      - Esther Gribelkis Pachter, 8/15/95, LEPA – 3. (MV110, MV191V) Transcript of Tape 3 of 6, 36 leaves (Box-folder 33/492)
      - Esther Gribelkis Pachter, 8/15/95, LEPA – 4. (MV111, MV191) Transcript of Tape 4 of 6, 32 leaves (Box-folder 33/493)
      - Esther Gribelkis Pachter, 8/15/95, LEPA – 5. (MV112, MV192) Transcript of Tape 5 of 6, 22 leaves (Box-folder 33/494)
      - Esther Gribelkis Pachter, 8/15/95, LEPA – 6. (MV113, MV193) Transcript of Tape 6 of 6, 27 leaves (Box-folder 33/495)
      - Esther Kessler, 5/24/95, LEK – 1. (MV102, MV177) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 1 of 6, 33 leaves (Box-folder 33/496)
      - Esther Kessler, 5/24/95, LEK – 2. (MV103, MV177) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 2 of 6, 30 leaves (Box-folder 33/497)
      - Esther Kessler, 5/24/95, LEK – 3. (MV104, MV177) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 3 of 6, 27 leaves (Box-folder 33/498)
      - Esther Kessler, 5/24/95, LEK – 4. (MV105, MV177) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 4, 29 leaves (Box-folder 33/499)
      - Esther Kessler, 5/24/95, LEK – 5. (MV106, MV178) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 5 of 6, 31 leaves (Box-folder 33/500)
      - Esther Kessler, 5/24/95, LEK – 6. (MV107, MV178) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 6 of 6, 18 leaves (Box-folder 33/501)
      - Esther Kessler Interview Corrected Transcript, Numbered Correction Inserts, 11 leaves. (Box-folder 33/502)
      - Victor Lichtmacher, 7/6/95, LVL – 1. (MV036, MV183, MV185) Transcript of Tape 1 of 7, 31 leaves (Box-folder 34/503)
      - Victor Lichtmacher, 7/6/95, LVL – 2. (MV037, MV183, MV185) Transcript of Tape 2 of 7, 30 leaves (Box-folder 34/504)
      - Victor Lichtmacher, 7/6/95, LVL – 3. (MV038, MV183, MV185), 32 leaves (Box-folder 34/505)
      - Victor Lichtmacher, 7/6/95, LVL – 4. (MV039, MV183, MV185), 33 leaves (Box-folder 34/506)
      - Victor Lichtmacher, 7/6/95, LVL – 5. (MV040, MV184, MV186), 26 leaves (Box-folder 34/507)
      - Victor Lichtmacher, 7/6/95, LVL – 6. (MV041, MV184, MV186), Transcript of Tape 6 of 7, 23 leaves (2 copies of page 21) (Box-folder 34/508)
      - Victor Lichtmacher, 7/6/95, LVL – 7. (MV042, MV184, MV186), Transcript of Tape 7 of 7, Transcript of Tape 5 of 7, 14 leaves (Box-folder 34/509)
      - Bernard Meller, 9/21/95, LBM – 1. (MV063, MV187, MV188) Transcript of Tape 1 of 8, 30 leaves (Box-folder 34/510)
      - Bernard Meller, 9/21/95, LBM – 2. (MV064, MV187, MV188) Transcript of Tape 2 of 8, 29 leaves (Box-folder 34/511)
      - Bernard Meller, 9/21/95, LBM – 3. (MV065, MV187, MV188) Transcript of Tape 3 of 8, 28 leaves (Box-folder 34/512)
      - Bernard Meller, 9/21/95, LBM – 4. (MV066, MV187, MV188) Transcript of Tape 4 of 8, 28 leaves (Box-folder 34/513)
      - Bernard Meller, 9/21/95, LBM – 5. (MV067, MV187, MV188) Transcript of Tape 5 of 8, 27 leaves (Box-folder 34/514)
      - Bernard Meller, 9/21/95, LBM – 6. (MV068, MV187, MV188) Transcript of Tape 6 of 8, 26 leaves (Box-folder 34/515)
      - Bernard Meller, 9/21/95, LBM – 7. (MV069, MV187, MV188) Transcript of Tape 7 of 8, 25 leaves (Box-folder 34/516)
      - Bernard Meller, 9/21/95, LBM – 8. (MV070, MV187, MV188) Transcript of Tape 8 of 8, 4 leaves (Box-folder 34/517)
      - Riwa Plotnik, 8/1/96, LRP – 1. (MV087, MV194) Transcript of Tape 1 of 7, 26 leaves (Box-folder 34/518)
      - Riwa Plotnik, 8/1/96, LRP – 2. (MV088, MV194) Transcript of Tape 2 of 7, 27 leaves (Box-folder 34/519)
      - Riwa Plotnik, 8/1/96, LRP – 3. (MV089, MV194) Transcript of Tape 3 of 7, 29 leaves (Box-folder 34/520)
      - Riwa Plotnik, 8/1/96, LRP – 4. (MV090, MV194) Transcript of Tape 4 of 7, 30 leaves (Box-folder 34/521)
      - Riwa Plotnik, 8/1/96, LRP – 5. (MV091, MV195) Transcript of Tape 5 of 7, 24 leaves (Box-folder 34/522)
      - Riwa Plotnik, 8/1/96, LRP – 6. (MV092, MV195) Transcript of Tape 6 of 7, 21 leaves (Box-folder 34/523)
      - Riwa Plotnik, 8/1/96, LRP – 7. (MV093, MV195) Transcript of Tape 7 of 7, 25 leaves (Box-folder 34/524)
      - Benjamin Rosenzweig, 7/10/95, LBR - 1. (MV114, MV199V, MV201) Transcript of Tape 1, 17 leaves (Box-folder 35/525)
      - Benjamin Rosenzweig, 7/10/95, LBR - 2. (MV115, MV199, MV201) Transcript of Tape 2, 22 leaves (Box-folder 35/526)
        Translated from Yiddish
      - Benjamin Rosenzweig, 7/10/95, LBR - 3. (MV116, MV199, MV201) Transcript of Tape 3, 20 leaves (Box-folder 35/527)
      - Benjamin Rosenzweig, 7/10/95, LBR - 4. (MV117, MV199, MV201) Transcript of Tape 4, 22 leaves (Box-folder 35/528)
      - Benjamin Rosenzweig, 7/10/95, LBR - 5. (MV118, MV200, MV202) Transcript of Tape 5, 26 leaves (Box-folder 35/529)
      - Benjamin Rosenzweig, 7/10/95, LBR - 6. (MV119, MV200, MV202) Copy 1 of transcript of Tape 6, 17 leaves (Box-folder 35/530)
      - Benjamin Rosenzweig, 7/10/95, LBR – 7. (MV120, MV200, MV202) Transcript of Tape 7, 7 leaves (Box-folder 35/531)
      - Moshe Shalev, 6/30/95, LMSH – 1. (MV076, MV203) Transcript of Tape 1 of 6, 26 leaves (Box-folder 35/532)
      - Moshe Shalev, 6/30/95, LMSH – 1. (MV076, MV203) Transcript of Tape 2 of 6, 26 leaves (Box-folder 35/533)
      - Moshe Shalev, 6/30/95, LMSH – 1. (MV076, MV203) Transcript of Tape 3 of 6, 26 leaves (Box-folder 35/534)
      - Moshe Shalev, 6/30/95, LMSH – 4. (MV079, MV203) Transcript of Tape 4 of 6, 23 leaves (Box-folder 35/535)
      - Moshe Shalev, 6/30/95, LMSH – 5. (MV080, MV204, MV205) Transcript of Tape 5 of 6, 21 leaves (Box-folder 35/536)
      - Moshe Shalev, 6/30/95, LMSH – 6. (MV081, MV204, MV205) Transcript of Tape 6 of 6, 11 leaves (Box-folder 35/537)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 1. (MV043, MV206, MV209) Transcripts of Tape 1 of 9, 29 leaves (Box-folder 35/538)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 2. (MV044, MV206, MV209) Transcripts of Tape 2 of 9, 28 leaves (Box-folder 35/539)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 3. (MV045, MV206, MV209) Transcripts of Tape 3 of 9, 28 leaves (Box-folder 35/540)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 4. (MV046, MV206, MV209) Transcripts of Tape 4 of 9, 27 leaves (Box-folder 35/541)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 5. (MV047, MV207, MV210) Transcripts of Tape 5 of 9, 25 leaves (Box-folder 35/542)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 6. (MV048, MV207, MV210) Transcripts of Tape 6 of 9, 22 leaves (Box-folder 35/543)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 7. (MV049, MV207, MV210) Transcripts of Tape 7 of 9, 22 leaves (Box-folder 35/544)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 8. (MV050, MV207, MV210) Transcripts of Tape 8 of 9, 22 leaves (Box-folder 35/545)
      - Nathan Sobel, 7/11/95, LNS – 9. (MV051, MV208, MV211) Transcripts of Tape 9 of 9, 20 leaves (Box-folder 35/546)
      - Aaron Ziegelman, 7/25/95, LAZ – 1. (MV054, MV214, MV219) Transcripts of Tape 1 of 6, 24 leaves (Box-folder 35/547)
      - Aaron Ziegelman, 7/25/95, LAZ – 2. (MV055, MV214, MV219) Transcripts of Tape 2 of 6, 24 leaves (Box-folder 35/548)
      - Aaron Ziegelman, 7/25/95, LAZ – 3. (MV056, MV214, MV219) Transcripts of Tape 3 of 6, 24 leaves (Box-folder 35/549)
      - Aaron Ziegelman, 7/25/95, LAZ – 4. (MV057, MV214, MV219) Transcripts of Tape 4 of 6, 25 leaves (Box-folder 35/550)
      - Aaron Ziegelman, 7/25/95, LAZ – 5. (MV058, MV215, MV220) Transcripts of Tape 5 of 6, 20 leaves (Box-folder 35/551)
      - Aaron Ziegelman, 7/25/95, LAZ – 6. (MV059, MV215, MV220) Transcripts of Tape 6 of 6, 7 leaves (Box-folder 35/552)
      - Aaron Ziegelman Interview Transcripts, August 6, 2001, 75 leaves (Box-folder 36/553)
        The Transciptions are in English.
    - Subseries 8: Luboml Documentary Project
      - Abraham (Abe) Getman Interview Transcript, August 6 Luboml Documentary Project, 2001, 114 leaves (Box-folder 36/554)
      - Aaron Ziegelman and Abraham Getman Interview Transcripts, August 7, 2001, 75 leaves (Box-folder 36/555)
      - Nathan (Nat) Sobel Interview Transcripts, August 7, 2001, 134 leaves (Box-folder 36/556)
        The Transcripts are in English.
      - Outline of Documentary - Douglas/Steinman Productions, September, 2001, 28 leaves (Box-folder 36/557)
      - Documentary Script and Scenes, December 3, 2001, 70 leaves (Box-folder 36/558)
      - Final Script (Printed), April 23, 2001, 51 leaves (Box-folder 36/559)
      - Post-Production Procedures, 2002, 15 leaves (Box-folder 36/560)
      - Promotional Material, 1995, 21 leaves (Box-folder 36/561)
      - Items Enclosed with Moving Image, 2002, 2 leaves (Box-folder 36/562)
        Item MV 263: Conversation between Aaron Ziegelman and Abe Getman in Olivne transcript of tapes 8-9 August 7th 2001 (copied from SR table).
    - Subseries 9: Artifact Documentation
      - Artifact Worksheets, Undated, 137 leaves (Box-folder 37/563)
      - Artifact Lists (Folder 1 of 2), Undated, 82 leaves (Box-folder 37/564)
      - Artifact Lists (Folder 2 of 2), Undated, 62 leaves, (1 black and white print) (Box-folder 37/565)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish and Hebrew/Yiddish.
      - Old Artifact List, Undated, 69 leaves (Box-folder 37/566)
      - New Artifact List, 45 leaves (Box-folder 37/567)
      - Photographs of Artifacts (Box-folder 37/568)
        2 black and white prints
      - Questions and Replies About Photographs (Box-folder 37/569)
      - Source Lists, 20 leaves (Box-folder 37/570)
      - Photographs and Artifacts from Mikola Dzei (Folder 1 of 3), 53 leaves, (1 color print) (Box-folder 37/571)
      - Photographs and Artifacts from Mikola Dzei (Folder 2 of 3) (01.2001-032.2001.), 3 leaves, (39 black and white prints) (Box-folder 37/572)
      - Photographs and Artifacts from Mikola Dzei (Folder 3 of 3) (033.2001-065.2001)., 1 leaf, (36 black and white prints) (Box-folder 37/573)
      - Slide Lists, 24 leaves (Box-folder 37/574)
      - Lists of Persons in Photographs, 78 leaves (Box-folder 37/575)
      - A1.1-A1.11. Gershengorn, 28 leaves, (14 photographs) (Box-folder 38/576)
        Loan Agreement and Deed of Gift
      - A2-TBO. Museum of Jewish Heritage, 7 leaves (Box-folder 38/577)
        3 Registration Forms
      - A3-TBO. Bokser (1 of 2), 20 leaves, (26 photographs) (Box-folder 38/578)
      - A3.1-A3.5. Bokser (2 of 2), 17 leaves, (5 photographs) (Box-folder 38/579)
      - A4.1-A4.2. Bravet (1 of 2), 2 leaves (Box-folder 38/580)
      - A4.1 – A4.2. Bravet (2 of 2), 10 leaves (Box-folder 38/581)
        Deed of Gift
      - A6.1 – A6.4. Cymerbojm (1 of 2), 5 leaves (Box-folder 38/582)
      - A6.1 – A6.4. Cymerbojm (2 of 2), 1 leaf 3 photographs, 1 artifact (Box-folder 38/583)
        Missing A6.4
      - A7.1 – A7.3. Chanales, 2 leaves, (3 photographs) (Box-folder 38/584)
      - A7.6. Chandles, 23 leaves, (5 photographs) (Box-folder 38/585)
      - A8.1, A8.3, A8-TBO. Eiger, 8 leaves, (5 photographs) (Box-folder 38/586)
      - A9.1. Halpern (1 of 2), 3 leaves (Box-folder 38/587)
      - A9.1. Halpern (1 of 2), 5 leaves, (1 photograph) (Box-folder 38/588)
      - A10.1 – A10.2. Hoch, 2 leaves, (19 photographs) (Box-folder 38/589)
        Loan Agreement
      - A11-TBO. Ingber, 12 leaves (Box-folder 38/590)
      - A12.1 – A12.11, A22.1. Karpus, 18 leaves, (15 photographs) (Box-folder 38/591)
        See oversize box: 2/18
      - A13.1 – A13.TBO. Kessler, 6 leaves (Box-folder 38/592)
      - A14.1 – A14.14. Koenigson (1 of 2), 9 leaves, (1 photograph) (Box-folder 38/593)
      - A14.1 – A14.14. Koenigson (2 of 2), 5 leaves, (14 photographs) (Box-folder 38/594)
      - A15.-TBO. Levine, 8 leaves (Box-folder 38/595)
      - A16.1 – A16.2. Lindenboym (1 of 2), 2 leaves (Box-folder 38/596)
      - A16.1 – A16.2. Lindenboym (2 of 2), 2 photographs (Box-folder 38/597)
      - A17.1-A17.4. Linder, 11 photographs (Box-folder 38/598)
        See oversize box: 2/30
      - A18.1 – A18.28. Nussenblatt, 25 leaves, (14 photographs) (Box-folder 38/599)
      - A18.1 – A18.28. Nussenblatt (1 of 2), 5 leaves, (60 photographs) (Box-folder 38/600)
      - A19-TBO. Schimmel, 8 leaves (Box-folder 38/601)
      - A20-TBO. Tesseler, 4 leaves (Box-folder 38/602)
        See oversize box: 2/25
      - A21-TBO. Strashun, 1 leaf (Box-folder 38/603)
      - A22.1 – A22.2, A12.1. Shavel, 2 leaves, (5 photographs) (Box-folder 38/604)
      - A23.1 – A23.7. Trofimowich (2 of 2), 4 leaves (Box-folder 38/605)
      - A23.1 – A23.7. Trofimowich (1 of 2), 35 leaves (Box-folder 38/606)
      - A24. Trokh, 35 photographs, (9 negatives) (Box-folder 38/607)
      - A25. Kraut (1 of 8), 56 leaves (Box-folder 39/608)
        Deed of Gift; Photocopy of photographs
      - A25. Kraut (2 of 8), 1 leaf (Box-folder 39/609)
        50 photographs
      - A25. Kraut (3 of 8), 1 leaf (Box-folder 39/610)
        19 photographs. Pre – 1938
      - A25. Kraut (4 of 8), 2 leaves (Box-folder 39/611)
        18 photographs
      - A25. Kraut (5 of 8), 2 leaves (Box-folder 39/612)
        27 photographs
      - A25. Kraut (6 of 8), 5 leaves (Box-folder 39/613)
        12 photographs
      - A25. Kraut (7 of 8), 1 leaf (Box-folder 39/614)
        12 photographs, 1 artifact
      - A25. Kraut (8 of 8), 5 leaves (Box-folder 39/615)
        1 photograph. Deed of Gift
      - A26.1 - A26.18. Dzei (1 of 3), 165 leaves (Box-folder 39/616)
        2 photographs, Photocopies of Diary Entries, Photocopies of Autograph, Book Entries, Photocopy of Nina Moyseyevitch’s Autograph Album, artifact. Photocopies of artifact A26.TBO.
        See oversize box 2/18
      - A26.19 - A26.49. Dzei (2 of 3), 72 leaves (Box-folder 39/617)
        33 photographs
      - A26.50 - A26.54, A26-TBO. Dzei A26 (3 of 3), 115 leaves (Box-folder 39/618)
        5 photographs
      - A27-TBO. Goodman, 13 leaves (Box-folder 39/619)
        7 photographs, Loan Agreement
      - A28. Golod (1 of 3) (Box-folder 39/620)
        2 photographs
      - A28. Golod (2 of 3) (Box-folder 39/621)
        19 photographs
      - A28. Golod (3 of 3), 3 leaves (Box-folder 39/622)
        46 photographs
      - A29. Fuchs, 1 leaf (Box-folder 39/623)
      - A30.1. Rodman, 3 leaves (Box-folder 39/624)
      - A30.1. Rodman (Box-folder 39/625)
        1 photograph
      - A31-TBO. Sobel (Box-folder 40/626)
        Photocopies of alcohol labels. Photocopies of other artifacts
      - A32.1 - A32.5. Ostapyuk, 12 leaves (Box-folder 40/627)
      - A33.1 - A33.4. Luboml Museum, 17 leaves (Box-folder 40/628)
        4 photographs
      - A33.2-A33.3. Luboml Museum, 15 leaves (Box-folder 40/629)
        Vodka labels
      - A34.2. Lictmacher, 94 leaves (Box-folder 40/630)
        4 photographs. See legal size box
      - A35-TBO. Gitalis, 2 leaves (Box-folder 40/631)
      - A36-TBO. Reden, 2 leaves (Box-folder 40/632)
        1 photograph, 18 color slides
      - A37.1-A37.6, A37-TBO. Ziegelman (1 of 2), 60 leaves (Box-folder 40/633)
      - A37.6. Ziegelman (2 of 2), 1 leaf (Box-folder 40/634)
      - A38.1 - A38.5. Orbuch (1 of 3), 69 leaves (Box-folder 40/635)
      - A38.2 - A38.18. Orbuch (2 of 3), 1 leaf (Box-folder 40/636)
        17 photographs. See legal size box
      - A38.1-A38.18, A38-TBO. Orbuch (3 of 3), 31 leaves, (10 photographs) (Box-folder 40/637)
        Deed of Gift, Interview of Sonia Orbuch
      - A39.1 - A39.30. Zim (1 of 3), 80 leaves, (5 photographs) (Box-folder 40/638)